Anssi Sirkiä CURRICULUM VITAE

050 5704896 anssisirkia@gmail.com

I am a highly motivated and versatile professional with a passion for both cooking and technology. My goal is to work as a web or software developer while constantly improving my skills and learning new things.

My experience in a busy and demanding restaurant environment has developed excellent skills in multitasking, problem-solving, and teamwork. My aim is to apply my analytical thinking, creativity, and precision to develop innovative and user-friendly software solutions.

Education

Haaga-Helia University of Applied Sciences 08.2021 -

Bachelor's degree,

Business Information Technology

Porvoon ammattiopisto 08.2010–05.2013

Restaurant Cook,

Vocational Qualification in Hotel and Restaurant Services

Experience

Employer	City	Date
Bumma Pizza & Bar Line Cook	Järvenpää	4.6.2023 – 1.9.2023
Ravintola Fryysarinranta Line Cook	Porvoo	28.04.2021 – 2.9.2021
Bistro Gustaf Line Cook	Porvoo	1.09.2019 – 19.4.2021
Ravintola Fryysarinranta Line Cook	Porvoo	27.04.2019 – 1.9.2019
B-Side Burgers Line Cook / Chef.	Porvoo	13.12.2017 – 1.12.2018
Ravintola Fryysarinranta Line Cook	Porvoo	01.05.2017 – 31.8.2017
Ravintola Fryysarinranta Line Cook	Porvoo	28.04.2016 – 1.9.2016
Ravintola Fryysarinranta Line Cook	Porvoo	01.05.2015 – 31.8.2015
Ravintola Fryysarinranta Line Cook	Porvoo	01.05.2014 – 31.8.2014
Ravintola Fryysarinranta Line Cook	Porvoo	01.05.2013 – 31.8.2013
Ravintola Fryysarinranta Line Cook	Porvoo	16.05.2012 – 31.08.2012

Anssi Sirkiä

CURRICULUM VITAE

050 5704896 anssisirkia@gmail.com

Languages

Finnish Native

English Full professional proficiency